Guide to the Committee on Bachelor of Arts Degree, Yale College, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Committee on Bachelor of Arts Degree, Yale College, Records
1898-1928
RU 583
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
0.75
(2 boxes)
The records consist of petitions and policies documenting the Committee on the Bachelor of Arts Degree at Yale College.
Yale College (1887- )
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 9-D (YRG 9-D), Records of Yale College Committees.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of petitions and policies documenting the Committee on the Bachelor of Arts Degree at Yale College.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by type of material.
Bachelor of arts degree; Degrees, Academic; Yale College (1887- ); Yale University -- Degrees
- Petitions, policy statements, and records, 1898-1928; Accession 1936-A-003
  - Petitions
    - 1898, 1901-1902, no date (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 1902-1903 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 1903-1904 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 1904-1905 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 1905-1906 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 1906-1907 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - 1907-1908 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 1908-1909 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 1909-1910 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - 1910-1911 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - 1911-1912 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - 1912-1913 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 1913-1914 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - 1905-1927 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Record of the actions of the committee, 1914-1928 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Policy re: granting of the B.A. degree, 1903-1914 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Policy re: combined course between Yale College and School of Medicine (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Policy re: discontinuance of the Ph.D. degree, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Petitions
    - 1914-1915 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - 1915-1916 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - 1916-1917 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - 1917-1919 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - 1919-1920 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - 1920-1921 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - 1922-1923 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - 1923-1924 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - 1924-1925 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - 1925-1926 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - 1926-1927 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - 1927-1928 (Box 2, Folder 30)